Wanna spend time playing the new
"Star Wars" game this weekend?
Mm, I don't know,
l promised myseIf l'd get off the computer...
(Leonard:)...be more physically active,
get some exercise.
(Howard:)You're about to walk up
three flights of stairs.
Well, good point. I'm in.
(Raj:)You know what would be great?
Let's do it like the old days.
- Mm, you talking gaming marathon?
- Yeah.
(Raj:)Start Saturday morning, go 48 hours,
sleeping bags, junk food.
(Howard:)Turn off our phones
so our moms can't call.
It'll be like our "World of warcraft" party
when the neighbors called the cops on us.
(Howard:)They called the cops because of the smell.
They thought we were dead.
(Raj:)We were bad-ass back in the day.
- All right, let's do it.
- Forty-eight hours of "Star wars" gaming.
(Raj:)It's on like Alderaan.
(Leonard:)Hey, Sheldon, clear your weekend.